tipidpc.com 2005-12-13

# 

**Privacy Policy**

For your privacy's protection, we at TipidPC.com use the following guidelines for users’ privacy. Signing up for an account at TipidPC.com means that you have read the following policies and have agreed to the associated terms. 

By signing up for an account with TipidPC, you agree to provide and maintain accurate, complete, and up-to-date information about yourself as required by the account creation process. 

All information collected by TipidPC will be used to: resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; benchmark consumer interest in our services; protect TipidPC and its users from fraud or any other criminal activity; and as otherwise described to the user at the time of collection. 

Upon your account's creation, all of your information is protected from other users by the provided login name and password. You are responsible for keeping your login information confidential and undisclosed. 

**UPDATED June 24, 2005**  
TPC warrants that it shall exercise diligence of a good father of a family to ensure privacy of any information collected from users. 

_However, TPC has the exclusive discretion as regards fair use of all content/data that passes through or is hosted by TPC, including the data that is transmitted via the Private Messaging tool; and TPC will not hesitate to report any content/data that promote the sale, purchase, or swap of pirated materials to the appropriate governmental office/s._

You agree that TipidPC may use personal information about you to analyze site usage, improve content and product offerings, and customize the site's layout and services. 

You agree that TipidPC may use personal information about you and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to its advertisers and sponsors for their marketing and promotional purposes. 

You agree that TipidPC can disclose personal information about you as requested by any law enforcement or government officials relating to any investigation or illegal activity. 

All relevant advisories posted in the Official News and Announcements thread shall form part of the TipidPC's Privacy Policy. 

TipidPC reserves the right to make changes to these policies at any time for any reason conceived by the Admins without prior notice.
